Guide to the News Service Biographical Files, circa 1930s - 2004
Duke University. University Archives
- Addition, 2004 [A2004-19] (Box 60)
  - Faculty and staff (Box 60)
    - Nadathur, Gopalan [Computer Science] (Box 89)
    - Nagaya, Hiroshi [DUMC] (Box 89)
    - Nagy, Paul D. [Psychiatry] (Box 89)
    - Nahm, Helen (Box 89)
    - Najam, Edward W. (Box 89)
    - Nash, Loy A. [Barber], 1970 (Box 89)
    - Nash, Thomas N. [Mechanical Engineering] (Box 89)
    - Nashold, Blaine S. [Neurosurgery] (Box 89)
    - Nathans, Elizabeth [Trinity College] (Box 89)
    - Nathans, Sydney [History] (Box 89)
    - Nau, Robert F. [Fuqua Business] (Box 89)
    - Naumann, Dorothy Ethel [DUMC], 1968 (Box 89)
    - Naylor, Aubreu W. [Botany] (Box 89)
    - Naylor, Thomas H. [Economics], before 1980 (Box 89)
    - Naylor, Thomas H. [Economics] (Box 89)
    - Nechay, Bohdan [Pharmacology ] (Box 89)
    - Nechyba, Thomas [Economics], 2002 (Box 89)
    - Needham, Amy [Psychology] (Box 89)
    - Needham, David [Mechanical Engineering] (Box 89)
    - Neelon, Francis [DUMC] (Box 89)
    - Nelius, Albert A. [Perkins Library], 1970 (Box 89)
    - Nelius, Sigrid Joanna [DUMC] (Box 89)
    - Nelson, Dalmas Hildor [Political Science] (Box 89)
    - Nelson, Eric B. [Marine Lab] (Box 89)
    - Nelson, Fletcher [Divinity School] (Box 89)
    - Nelson, Larry [Health Affairs] (Box 89)
    - Nelson, Norman K. (Box 89)
    - Nelson, Roland H. (Box 89)
    - Nemeroff, Charles B. [Psychoneuroendocrinology] (Box 89)
    - Nesbitt, M. Wilson [Divinity School] (Box 89)
    - Neurath, Hans [Biochemistry ] (Box 89)
    - Neuschel, Kristen [History] (Box 89)
    - Nevidjon, Brenda [DUMC] (Box 89)
    - Neville, Jerry [Pediatrics] (Box 89)
    - Nevins, Joseph R. [Microbiology and Immunology] (Box 89)
    - Newbern, Kathy [News Science] (Box 89)
    - Newborg, Barbara [DUMC] (Box 89)
    - Newby, Kristen [Cardiology ] (Box 89)
    - Newcomer, Dorothy F. [Physical Education] (Box 89)
    - Newgard, Christopher, 2002 (Box 89)
    - Newman, Francis Wesley [Technical Services], 1985 (Box 89)
    - Newman, Gustave [Psychiatry], 1960 (Box 89)
    - Newman, Mark [DUMC] (Box 89)
    - Newman, Theresa [Law], 2000 (Box 89)
    - Newton, Francis [Classical Studies] (Box 89)
    - Newton, John Garland [Marine Lab] (Box 89)
    - Nichitta, Christopher [Cell Biology], 1999 (Box 89)
    - Nichol, Archibald Jamieson [Economics] (Box 89)
    - Nichols, Claude R. [Psychiatry], 1960 (Box 89)
    - Nichols, Jack L. (Box 89)
    - Nichols, Madeline W. [Latin American Studies] (Box 89)
    - Nicholson, Dennis B. [Architecture] (Box 89)
    - Nicholson, William M. [DUMC] (Box 89)
    - Nicklas, Robert Bruce [Zoology] (Box 90)
    - Nicolelis, Miguel [Romance Languages] (Box 90)
    - Nightengale, Kathryn, 2002 (Box 90)
    - Nijhout, H. Frederik [Zoology] (Box 90)
    - Niklason, Laura [DUMC], 1999 (Box 90)
    - Nisbet, Caroline [Duke Futures] (Box 90)
    - Nixon, Nan [Fed. Relations] (Box 90)
    - Noble, John (Box 90)
    - Noble, W. Lee [Business] (Box 90)
    - Noell, Karl [Radiation Therapy], 1979 (Box 90)
    - Noland, William [Art] (Box 90)
    - Nolte, Henry R., Jr. (Box 90)
    - Nolte, Loren W. [Engineering] (Box 90)
    - Noojin, Ray O. [Dermatology and Syphilology], 1945 (Box 90)
    - Nordheim, Lother W. (Box 90)
    - Nordstrom, Robert J. [Law], 1968 (Box 90)
    - Noren, Carol M. [Divinity School] (Box 90)
    - Norris, John D. (Box 90)
    - North, Jeremy (Box 90)
    - North, William C. [DUMC] (Box 90)
    - Northington, Betty Page (Box 90)
    - Novak, Richey A. [German Studies] (Box 90)
    - Nowicki, Stephen [Zoology] (Box 90)
    - Nowlin, John B. [Student Health] (Box 90)
    - Nozaki, Yosuhiko [Biochemistry] (Box 90)
    - Nuermberger, G. A., 1943 (Box 90)
    - Nunley, James A. [Orthopaedic Surgery] (Box 90)
    - Nunn, Henry P. (Box 90)
    - Nygard, Holger Olof [English Studies] (Box 90)
    - Nygard, Margaret, 1995 (Box 90)
    - Oas, Terrence G. [Biochemistry], 1997 (Box 90)
    - Oates, John F. [Classical Studies] (Box 90)
    - O'Barr, Jean [Women's Studies], before 1980 (Box 90)
    - O'Barr, Jean [Women's Studies] (Box 90)
    - O'Barr, William [Cultural Anthropology] (Box 90)
    - O'Conner, Thomas J. [Aerospace Studies], 1986 (Box 90)
    - O'Conner, Christopher [Cardiology] (Box 90)
    - O'Conner Patricia [Placement Services] (Box 90)
    - Oddone, Eugene [General Medicine], 1999 (Box 90)
    - Odom, Guy L. [Neurosurgery] (Box 90)
    - Odum, Howard Thomas [Zoology], 1956 (Box 90)
    - Oehler, Serri M. [DUMC], 1984 (Box 90)
    - O'Foghludha, Feargus [Radiology] (Box 90)
    - Ogburn, Sandy [Community Affairs] (Box 90)
    - Oh, Seog [Physics] (Box 90)
    - O'Hara, Sara [Pedicatric Radiology] (Box 90)
    - O'Hara, Sara [Pedicatric Radiology], 1998 (Box 90)
    - Ohman, Erik [Cardiology] (Box 90)
    - Ohman, Magnus [DUMC], 2001 (Box 90)
    - Olansky, Sidney [Dermatology ] (Box 90)
    - Olcutt, Martha Brill, 1992 (Box 90)
    - Oldham, H. Newland [Surgery] (Box 90)
    - Oldham, R. T. [Aerospace Studies] (Box 90)
    - O'Leary, James Sohn [Economics] (Box 90)
    - Olela, Henry [Black Studies], 1974 (Box 90)
    - Oleson, James R. [Radiation ] (Box 90)
    - Olive, Billy Brown (Box 90)
    - Oliver, Henry M. [Economics] (Box 90)
    - Oliver, Mary [English ], 1995 (Box 90)
    - Olsen, Elise A. [Dermatology] (Box 90)
    - Olson, Janice [Hematology and Oncology], 1996 (Box 90)
    - O'Neal, Hodge [Law] (Box 90)
    - O'Neill, Bernard V., Sr. [Mathematics], 1968 (Box 90)
    - Onken, Jane [Gastro], 1999 (Box 90)
    - Onley, David S. [Physics], 1963 (Box 90)
    - O'Quinn, Aglaia N. [Psychiatry] (Box 90)
    - O'Quinn, Lea (Box 90)
    - O'Rand, Angela M. [Sociology] (Box 90)
    - Orbach, Michael K. [Marine Lab] (Box 90)
    - Orgain, Edward Stuart [Cardiology] (Box 90)
    - Ormandy, Roderick B. [DUMC], 1963 (Box 90)
    - Orr, Linda [Romance Languages] (Box 90)
    - Orsini, Napoleone (Box 90)
    - Osborn, Robert [Religion] (Box 91)
    - Osborne, James G. [Forestry], 1968 (Box 91)
    - Osborne, William J. [University Union] (Box 91)
    - Osmond, Barry C. [Botany] (Box 91)
    - Osterhout, Shirley [Poison Control], 1975-1985 (Box 91)
    - Osterhout, Shirley [Poison Control], 1986-1995 (Box 91)
    - Osterhout, Suydam [Microbiology] (Box 91)
    - Ostrowski, Michael C. [Microbiology and Immunology], 1985 (Box 91)
    - Osuna, Raphael [Romance Languages], 1977 (Box 91)
    - O'Sullivan, William I [Chemistry], 1959 (Box 91)
    - Ottolenghi, Athos [Pharmacology] (Box 91)
    - Overhauser, David Vincent [Electrical Engineering], 1994 (Box 91)
    - Overman, John R. [Microbiology] (Box 91)
    - Owen, Edward E. [Medicine], 1962 (Box 91)
    - Owen, Harry Ashton, Jr. [Electrical Engineering] (Box 91)
    - Owen, William F., Jr. [Medicine], 2001 (Box 91)
    - Padilla, George M. [Physiology] (Box 91)
    - Page, Ellis B. [Education and Psychology], 1983 (Box 91)
    - Page, Ellis B. [Education and Psychology] (Box 91)
    - Paletz, David L. [Political Science] (Box 91)
    - Palmer, Michael J. [Office of Community Affairs] (Box 91)
    - Palmer, Richard A. [Chemistry] (Box 91)
    - Palmer, Richard Geoffrey [Physics] (Box 91)
    - Palmer, Scott [DUMC], 2002 (Box 91)
    - Palmore, Erdman [Sociology] (Box 91)
    - Pardon, William Leslie [Mathematics] (Box 91)
    - Pardue, Leonard G. [University Relations], 1987-1989 (Box 91)
    - Parker, Clarence M. [Sports] (Box 91)
    - Parker, Harold [History], 2000 (Box 91)
    - Parker, Keith L. [Medicine] (Box 91)
    - Parker, Roy T. [Gynecology] (Box 91)
    - Parker, Scott J. [Theater] (Box 91)
    - Parkerson, George R. [Medicine] (Box 91)
    - Parkerson, Mary [Duke Chapel] (Box 91)
    - Parkins, Robert C. [Organist] (Box 91)
    - Parkinson, Russell S. [History] (Box 91)
    - Parmigiani, Giovanni [Statistics and Decision Sciences], 1999 (Box 91)
    - Parnell, Allan [Sociology], 1993 (Box 91)
    - Parsons, Beth (Box 92)
    - Partan, Daniel G. [Law] (Box 92)
    - Partin, Harry B. [Religion] (Box 92)
    - Partner, Simon [History] (Box 92)
    - Pas, Eric I. [Civil Engineering] (Box 92)
    - Pasipoularides, Ares D. [Biomedical Engineering] (Box 92)
    - Passaro, Joanne [Cultural Anthropology] (Box 92)
    - Pate, Ned [DUMC], 2002 (Box 92)
    - Patel, Dhavalkumar [Rheumatology and Immunology], 1996 (Box 92)
    - Patel, Vijay [DUMC], 2002 (Box 92)
    - Patrick, Merrell L. [Computer Science] (Box 92)
    - Petroski, Henry [Engineering], 2001 (Box 92)
    - Patterson, Annabel M. [English] (Box 92)
    - Patterson, David T. [Botany] (Box 92)
    - Patterson, Eugene, 1971 (Box 92)
    - Patterson, Lee [English] (Box 92)
    - Patterson, Randolph Fleming [Naval Science] (Box 92)
    - Patz, Edward F. [Radiology] (Box 92)
    - Paulson, David F. [Urology and Surgery] (Box 92)
    - Pavlov, Michael I. [Russian] (Box 92)
    - Payne, Bruce [Political Science and Public Affairs] (Box 92)
    - Payne, Charles M. [History] (Box 92)
    - Payne, John W. [Fuqua Business] (Box 92)
    - Peach, William Bernard [Philosophy] (Box 92)
    - Pearsall, George W. [Mechanical Engineering] (Box 92)
    - Pearse, A. S. [Zoology] (Box 92)
    - Pearson, Birger A. [Religion] (Box 92)
    - Peele, Talmage [DUMC] (Box 92)
    - Peete, Charles H., Jr. [Obstetrics and Gynecology] (Box 92)
    - Peete, William Pettway [Surgery] (Box 92)
    - Pell, Charles A. [Bio Design Studio] (Box 92)
    - Pendergast, Ann Marie [Pharmacology] (Box 92)
    - Pepper, Joseph and Barbara [Music] (Box 92)
    - Peretto, Pietro F. [Economics] (Box 92)
    - Perez, Gustavo [Romance Languages] (Box 92)
    - Perfect, John [Medicine] (Box 92)
    - Pericak-Vance, Margaret [Neurology] (Box 92)
    - Perkins, Ronald D. [Geology] (Box 92)
    - Perry, C. W. (Box 92)
    - Perry, Edmund F. [Religion] (Box 92)
    - Perry, Francis [Music] (Box 92)
    - Perry, Henry [Medicine] (Box 92)
    - Persing, E. U. [Nursing] (Box 92)
    - Persons, Elizabeth A. [Women's College] (Box 92)
    - Persons, Susan L. [Admissions], 1968 (Box 92)
    - Persons, Walter [Swimming] (Box 92)
    - Peter, Robert Halton [Cardiology] (Box 92)
    - Peters, Kevin G. [Cardiology] (Box 92)
    - Peters, Melvin K. [Religion] (Box 92)
    - Peters, William [Hematology and Oncology] (Box 92)
    - Peterson, David W. [Fuqua Business; Law] (Box 92)
    - Peterson, Eric [Cardiology] (Box 92)
    - Petrowski, Henry [Civil Engineering], 1983-1989 (Box 92)
    - Petrowski, Henry [Civil Engineering], 1990-1995 (Box 92)
    - Petrowski, Henry [Civil Engineering], 1996-2002 (Box 92)
    - Petrow, Vladimir [Physiology], 1979 (Box 92)
    - Petrusa, Emil R. [Surgery] (Box 92)
    - Petters, Arlie [Mathematics] (Box 92)
    - Petty, Olan L. [Education] (Box 92)
    - Peyroux, Catherine [History] (Box 92)
    - Pfeiffer, Eric [Institute of Aging] (Box 92)
    - Pfeiffer, John, Jr. [Medicine] (Box 92)
    - Phelps, Jon J. [University Union] (Box 92)
    - Phelps, Leland R. [Germanic Language and Literature], 1988 (Box 92)
    - Philbrick, Donna Rae [Fuqua Business] (Box 92)
    - Phillips, Harry R. III [Medicine] (Box 92)
    - Phillips, Paula Ruth [Women] (Box 92)
    - Philpott, Jane [Botany] (Box 92)
    - Piantadosi, Claude [Pulmonary Medicine], 1999 (Box 92)
    - Pickett, Henry F. [Photography] (Box 92)
    - Pickrell, Kenneth L. [Surgery] (Box 92)
    - Pickus, Noah [Public Policy] (Box 92)
    - Piehler, Henry, 1979 (Box 92)
    - Pieper, Carl F., 1998 (Box 92)
    - Pieper, Carl F., 2002 (Box 92)
    - Pierce, J. Jeffrey [Civil Engineering] (Box 92)
    - Pierce-Baker, Charlotte [English], 1999 (Box 92)
    - Pietrantoni, J. G. [Auxillaries] (Box 92)
    - Pilkey, Orrin H. [Geologist], 1965-1969 (Box 93)
    - Pilkey, Orrin H. [Geologist], 1970 (Box 93)
    - Pilkey, Orrin H. [Geologist], 1973 (Box 93)
    - Pilkey, Orrin H. [Geologist], 1974-1977 (Box 93)
    - Pilkey, Orrin H. [Geologist], 1979 (Box 93)
    - Pilkey, Orrin H. [Geologist], 1980 (Box 93)
    - Pilkey, Orrin H. [Geologist], 1981 (Box 93)
    - Pilkey, Orrin H. [Geologist], 1982 (Box 93)
    - Pilkey, Orrin H. [Geologist], 1983-84 (Box 93)
    - Pilkey, Orrin H. [Geologist], 1984 (Box 93)
    - Pilkey, Orrin H. [Geologist], 1985 (Box 93)
    - Pilkey, Orrin H. [Geologist], 1986 (Box 93)
    - Pilkey, Orrin H. [Geologist], 1987 (Box 93)
    - Pilkey, Orrin H. [Geologist], 1988 (Box 94)
    - Pilkey, Orrin H. [Geologist], 1989 (Box 94)
    - Pilkey, Orrin H. [Geologist], 1991 (Box 94)
    - Pilkey, Orrin H. [Geologist], 1992 (Box 94)
    - Pilkey, Orrin H. [Geologist], 1993 (Box 94)
    - Pilkey, Orrin H. [Geologist], 1994- (Box 94)
    - Pilkey, Orrin H. [Geologist], 1999 (Box 94)
    - Pilkey, Orrin H. [Geologist] (Box 94)
    - Pilkington, Theo C. [Biomedical Engineering ], d. 1/6/1993 (Box 94)
    - Pinnell, Sheldon R. [Dermatologist] (Box 94)
    - Pinnell, Sheldon R. [Dermatologist], 2001 (Box 94)
    - Piot, Charles D. [Cultural Anthropology] (Box 94)
    - Pircher, Felix J. [Radiologist] (Box 94)
    - Pirrung, Michael C. [Chemist], 1990-2001 (Box 94)
    - Piscitelli, Joanne [Gynecologist], 1985 (Box 94)
    - Pisetsky, David Stephen [Rheumatology and Immunology], 1985-2000 (Box 94)
    - Pitman, Kathy C. [News Service] (Box 94)
    - Pitts, Elizabeth LaRocca [Divinity School], 2001 (Box 94)
    - Piva, John J. [Office of the for Alumni Affairs and Development], 1987-1991 (Box 94)
    - Pizzo, Salvatore [Pathology and Biochemistry], -2001 (Box 94)
    - Platt, Jeffrey L. [Surgery] (Box 94)
    - Plonsey, Robert [Biomedical Engineering; Physiology] (Box 94)
    - Plummer, Ellen [Women's Center] (Box 94)
    - Poirier, Jacques Charles [Chemist], 1956-76 (Box 94)
    - Polascik, Thomas [Urology], 2002 (Box 94)
    - Politano, Victor A. [Urology], 1962 (Box 94)
    - Politi, Elisabetta, 2001 (Box 94)
    - Pollack, Sheldon V. [Dermatologist] (Box 94)
    - Polniaszck, Richard Paul [Chemist] (Box 94)
    - Polt, Sarah S. [Pathology ], 1960s (Box 94)
    - Pope, Deborah [English], 1985-97 (Box 94)
    - Pope, Deborah [English], 2001 (Box 94)
    - Porter, Calvin Lewis [Divinity School], 1961-62 (Box 94)
    - Porter, Ned Allen [Chemist], 1980s (Box 94)
    - Porter, Joseph [English], 1985-2001 (Box 94)
    - Portwood, Richard M. [Medicine], 1958-71 (Box 94)
    - Postlethwait, Raymond W. [Surgeon], 1989 (Box 94)
    - Posy, Carl J. [Philosophy] (Box 94)
    - Poteat, William [Religion] (Box 94)
    - Potter, Michael R. [Forestry and Environmental Studies], 1986 (Box 94)
    - Pounds, Lois [Pediatrics; Medical Education], 1996 (Box 94)
    - Polanyi, Michael [Religion], 1963 (Box 95)
    - Powell, H. Jefferson [Law and Divinity], 1991-2000 (Box 95)
    - Powell, Richard J. [Art History], of art history dept. through June 30 1999 (Box 95)
    - Powell, Rufus H. III [Secretary ], 1994 (Box 95)
    - Pratt, Ella Fountain [Office of Cultural Affairs], 1990 (Box 95)
    - Pratt, Philip C. [Pathology] (Box 95)
    - Pratt, Vernon Gaither [Art ], d. 2/27/2000 (Box 95)
    - Pratt, Walter F. [Law], 1984 (Box 95)
    - Predmore, Richard L. [Grad Arts and Sciences] (Box 95)
    - Preiss, Jack J. [Sociology], 1987 (Box 95)
    - Preston, Richard A. [Canadian Studies] (Box 95)
    - Preston, William [Psychiatry], 1979 (Box 95)
    - Price, David Eugene [Political Science], 1974-84 (Box 95)
    - Price, David Eugene [Political Science], 1985 (Box 95)
    - Price, David Eugene [Political Science], 1986 (Box 95)
    - Price, David Eugene [Political Science], 1987-92 (Box 95)
    - Price, David Eugene [Political Science], 1993- (Box 95)
    - Price, Matthew [Cultural Anthropology] (Box 95)
    - Price, James L., Jr. [Religion], 1974-96 (Box 95)
    - Price, Reynolds [English] (Box 95)
    - Pride, Cletis [Duke University News Service], 1969-84 (Box 95)
    - Prisant, Michael [Chemistry], 1990-97 (Box 95)
    - Pritchard, Eric [Music], 1995-96 (Box 95)
    - Pritchett, Edward [Cardiologist], 1984-98 (Box 95)
    - Proctor, Jesse H., Jr. [Political Science], 1958 (Box 95)
    - Proctor, Samuel DeWitt [Divinity], d. 5/22/1997 (Box 95)
    - Proia, Alan [Opthamologist; Pathologist], 1984 (Box 95)
    - Prosnitz, Leonard R. [Radiologist], 1984-1996 (Box 95)
    - Pryor, David M. [Cardiologist], 1991-94 (Box 95)
    - Pugh, Stefan M. [Slavic Languages] (Box 95)
    - Puma, Joseph A. [Cardiologist], 1995 (Box 95)
    - Purohit, Debu [Fuqua Business, Marketing], 1991-2002 (Box 95)
    - Purves, Dale [Neurobiologist], 1990-2000 (Box 95)
    - Putallaz, Martha [Psychologist], 1986-1993 (Box 95)
    - Putman, Charles E. [Radiologist; Vice Provost], 1985-92 (Box 96)
    - Putman, Charles E. [Radiologist; Vice Provost], 1993-99 (Box 96)
    - Pyatt, Tim [University Archivist], 2002 (Box 96)
    - Pye, Kenneth A. [President Duke and SMU], 1987-94 (Box 96)
    - Pyne, James Minitree [Duke Hospital], 1949-56 (Box 96)
    - Qualls, Robert G. [the Environment], 1994 (Box 96)
    - Quill, Timothy J. [Anesthesiology], 1985-89 (Box 96)
    - Quilligan, Maureen [English Dept.], 1999-2000 (Box 96)
    - Quin, Louis D. [Chemistry], 1959 (Box 96)
    - Quinlan, Alician Veronica [Engineering (biochemical and mechanical)] (Box 96)
    - Quinn, Naomi [Anthropologist] (Box 96)
    - Rabin, David [Engineer], 1957 (Box 96)
    - Radtke, Rodney A. [Neurologist], 1995 (Box 96)
    - Radway, Janice A. [Literature and English], 1994-99 (Box 96)
    - Raetz, Christian R. H. [Biochemist], 1993-2001 (Box 96)
    - Raimi, Frederic B. [Cellist], 1974-98 (Box 96)
    - Raimi, Mary Eliza Jane (professional name: Jane Hawkins) [Music Dept.] (Box 96)
    - Rainey, Harry "Uncle Harry", d. 3/17/1993 (Box 96)
    - Rainey, Thomas B., Jr. [Historian], 1966-67 (Box 96)
    - Rainwater, Roland W. [Religious Activities] (Box 96)
    - Raitt, Jill [Theology], 1975-80 (Box 96)
    - Raj, Ganesh [Urologist], 2002 (Box 96)
    - Rajagopalan, K. V. [Biochemist], 1977-85 (Box 96)
    - Ralston, Charles W. [Forestry School], 1983 (Box 96)
    - Ramirez-Rivera, Jose [Medicine], 1969 (Box 96)
    - Ramus, Joseph S. [Botanist], 1985-2000 (Box 96)
    - Randall, Dale B. [English], 1960-99 (Box 96)
    - Raney, Richard B. [Othopaedics], 1941 (Box 96)
    - Rankin, Thomas S. [Doc. Studies], 1998-99 (Box 96)
    - Rao, Sunil [Doctor], 2002 (Box 96)
    - Rapaport, Elizabeth [Public Policy] (Box 96)
    - Raspberry, William [Journalism], 1995-2001 (Box 96)
    - Raspberry, William [Minority Affairs] (Box 96)
    - Rasmussen, Ann Marie [Germanic Language] (Box 96)
    - Rausher, Mark D. [Zoologist], 1989 (Box 96)
    - Ravin, Carl E. [Radiologist], 1978-85 (Box 96)
    - Ravin, Carl E. [Radiologist], 1991 (Box 96)
    - Ravitz, L. J. [Psychiatrist], 1951 (Box 96)
    - Rawlings, James, 1998 (Box 96)
    - Raynor, Calla Ann [Health, P.E. and Recreation], 1968 (Box 96)
    - Read, Andrew [Biologist] (Box 96)
    - Reamer, I. Thomas [Pharmacist], 1968 (Box 96)
    - Reckhow, Kenneth H. [Civil Engineer], 1996-2000 (Box 96)
    - Reckless, John [Psychiatrist], 1974 (Box 96)
    - Redding, Francis [Music Dept.], 1969 (Box 96)
    - Reddy, William M. [Historian], 1980-96 (Box 96)
    - Redick, Lloyd F. [Anesthesiology and Obstetrics and Gynecology Depts.] (Box 96)
    - Reed, Frederick J. [Engineer] (Box 96)
    - Reed, Mark D. [Sociology], 1991-92 (Box 96)
    - Reed, Michael Charles, 1974- (Box 96)
    - Reed, Wallace Elzie [Economist], 1996 (Box 96)
    - Reedy, Michael K. [Anatomy; Physiology], 2001 (Box 96)
    - Reents-Budet, Dorie [Art Museum] (Box 96)
    - Rees, Joe Curtis [Librarian], 1971 (Box 96)
    - Reeves, Robert J. [Radiologist], 1962 (Box 96)
    - Reichert, William M. [Biomedical Engineer], 1988 (Box 96)
    - Reid, John T. [Spanish], 1940 (Box 96)
    - Reif, John H. [Computer Science], 1987-2000 (Box 96)
    - Reilly, Edward [Law], 1972 (Box 96)
    - Reimann, Donald H. (Box 96)
    - Reimer, Keith [Pathologist], 1983 (Box 96)
    - Reinthal, Peter [Zoologist], 1986 (Box 96)
    - Reisner, Emily [Pathologist], 1982-85 (Box 96)
    - Reller, L. Barth [Pathologist], 1997-98 (Box 96)
    - Reppy, William Amell, Jr. [Law], 1980-97 (Box 96)
    - Rerych, Stephen K. [Surgeon] (Box 96)
    - Reves, Joseph Gerald [Anesthesiology], 1984-90 (Box 96)
    - Reynolds, Jacqueline [Physiology] (Box 96)
    - Reynolds, James [Botanist], 1996-99 (Box 96)
    - Rezvani, Amir [UNC], 1999 (Box 96)
    - Rhoads, John MacFarlane [Psychiatrist], 1962-80 (Box 96)
    - Rice, Charles Lynvel [Divinity School], 1968 (Box 96)
    - Rice, Henry [Surgeon], 2002 (Box 96)
    - Rice, John Russell [Rheumatology; Immunology], 1978 (Box 96)
    - Rice, Louise [Art History], 1994-95 (Box 96)
    - Richard, Jean Francois [Statistics and Decision Science], 1989 (Box 96)
    - Richards, John F. [Historian] (Box 96)
    - Richardson, Curtis J. [Forestry and Environmental Studies], 1975-99 (Box 96)
    - Richardson, Curtis J. [Forestry and Environmental Studies], 2001 (Box 96)
    - Richardson, David C. [Biochemistry], 1991- (Box 96)
    - Richardson, Jane S. [Biochemistry], Before 1993 (Box 96)
    - Richardson, Jane S. [Biochemistry], 1993- (Box 96)
    - Richardson, Lawrence, Jr. [Classical Studies], 1966-86 (Box 96)
    - Richey, McMurry Smith [Divinity School], 1956-1982 (Box 96)
    - Richey, Russell Earle [Divinity School] (Box 96)
    - Richey, Russell Earle [Divinity School], 1994 (Box 96)
    - Richter, Daniel [Forestry and Environmental Science], 1988-2001 (Box 96)
    - Richtsmeier, William [Otolaryngology] (Box 96)
    - Ricks, William E. [Business], 1985 (Box 96)
    - Riddell, Richard V. [Drama], Before 1993 (Box 96)
    - Riddell, Richard V. [Drama], 1993 (Box 96)
    - Riddell, Richard V. [Drama], 1994 (Box 96)
    - Riebel, John D., retired 12/31/87 (Box 96)
    - Riefkohl, Ronald [Plast/Reconst; Maxillofacial/Oral Surgery] (Box 96)
    - Rierson, Michael D. (Box 96)
    - Riggens, Greg J. [Pathology; Genetics] (Box 96)
    - Rigsby, Kent Jefferson [Classical Studies] (Box 96)
    - Riley, Margaret [Study Abroad], 2001 (Box 96)
    - Rimer, Barbara [Cancer Center] (Box 96)
    - Riordan, Mary Ellen Bohl [Physical Therapy] (Box 96)
    - Ripley, Dana Phelps [Romance Languages] (Box 96)
    - Riski, John E. (Box 96)
    - Ritchie, George Henry (Box 96)
    - Ritchie, B. Maurice [Divinity School] (Box 96)
    - Rittschof, Daniel [Environment] (Box 96)
    - Roalfe, William R. (Box 96)
    - Roberson, David (Box 96)
    - Roberson, Russell [Physics] (Box 96)
    - Robert, Joseph C. (Box 96)
    - Roberts, Darryl Lamont [Political Science] (Box 96)
    - Roberts, J. Deotis [Divinity School] (Box 96)
    - Roberts, Jesse [Rheumatology Immunology] (Box 96)
    - Roberts, John H. (Box 96)
    - Roberts, Jim [Academic Budget Officer] (Box 96)
    - Robertson, Cary [Urology] (Box 96)
    - Robertson, Horace [Law] (Box 96)
    - Robertson, James David (Box 96)
    - Robinson, C. K. (Box 96)
    - Robinson, Clyde O., Jr. (Box 96)
    - Robinson, George (Box 96)
    - Robinson, H. G. [Physics] (Box 96)
    - Robinson, Sandra P. [Religion] (Box 96)
    - Robisheaux, Tom [History] (Box 97)
    - Robl, Hermann R. (Box 97)
    - Rockey, Don Chase [Medicine] (Box 97)
    - Rockwell, Kenneth [Psychiatry; CAPS] (Box 97)
    - Roderick, Marshall R. [Philosophy] (Box 97)
    - Rodio, Carmen J. [Laboratory Animal Resources] (Box 97)
    - Rodriquez, Gustavo [Dept. Obstetrics and Gynecology, Oncology Division] (Box 97)
    - Roe, Charles R. [Genetics and Metabolism] (Box 97)
    - Rogers, Charles Allen [Divinity School] (Box 97)
    - Rogers, Mark Charles (Box 97)
    - Rogers, R. S. III (Box 97)
    - Roggli, Victor [Pathology] (Box 97)
    - Rohlf, Richard J. [Counseling Center] (Box 97)
    - Rojstaczer, Stuart [Geology] (Box 97)
    - Rojstaczer, Stuart [Geology], 2001 (Box 97)
    - Roland, Alex [History] (Box 97)
    - Rolleston, James L. [Germanic Languages and Literature] (Box 97)
    - Romanelli, Elaine [Fuqua Business] (Box 97)